## Tim Lewis Cell: 720-418-0533

Email: timothydlewis@icloud.com

**LinkedIn:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/gunfightingyeti **Website:** https://gunfightingyeti.github.io/Assignment3/Bootstrap%20Website/index.html

**Github:** https://github.com/GunFightingYeti

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

#### HARD WORKING - DEDICATED - QUICK LEARNER - PROBLEM SOLVING

Extremely hard working. Cares greatly about impacting the surrounding community for the better. Values honesty and integrity as core principles in work and life. Strives to produce high quality results. Skill sets in varying backgrounds contributes to the ability to adapt quickly. Experience in managing other employees and large groups of individuals. No challenge is too small, and no puzzle is unsolvable.

- Personal Safety Multiple 2<sup>nd</sup> Dan Black Belts
- Leadership
- Technical Support
- Organization and Planning
- Critical Thinking

- Customer service
- Public Speaking
- Personal Fitness
- Developer
- Design

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Denver University - Full Stack Developer Bootcamp Developer

Denver, Colorado July 2018 – January 2019

A challenging program with an extensive curriculum that covers full stack development, including; HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, PHP, Laravel, Express.js, React.js, Database Theory, Bookshelf.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, Git, and more. This is an incredible program meant to give a wide range of skills in coding and development.

# **Spectrum Retirement Director of Maintenance**

Centennial, Colorado December 2016 – Present

As DOM my job is to make sure my community runs smoothly. I am responsible for every part of the building inside and out. My daily tasks include: Work order completion/resident requests, apartment make readies, preventative maintenance, systems upkeep, cleanliness, atmosphere of the building and vendor relations. I aim to make our community look and run like a high-end hotel but feel like a home.

#### Responsibilities as Director of Maintenance:

- Work Orders My goal is to address work orders the day they are received so residents feel their request is answered promptly, respectfully and cheerfully.
- Apartment Make Readies Patch and paint walls, shampoo carpet, cleaning, general fixes.
- Atmosphere This is by far the most difficult to achieve. I have found that most of the look and feel of a building depends on the attitude of staff and management. I choose to lead by example, keeping my attitude positive and being willing to step in whenever necessary to get results.
- Vendor Relations Maintaining positive working relationships with various vendors and overseeing projects as needed.

# MorningStar Senior Living at Dayton Place Maintenance Assistant

Denver, Colorado June 2016 – December 2016

As a Maintenance Assistant my job was primarily completing work orders, preventative maintenance and completing room turns. Daily tasks were very similar to my work with Spectrum Retirement.

My primary job at Premier Martial Arts was Head Instructor, which consisted of teaching classes and running events and seminars. Within my work as Head Instructor I was also responsible for technical support, managing other employees, marketing, customer service, maintenance, and cleaning.

#### Responsibilities as Head Instructor:

- Teach all ages from 3 years old to adult
- Instruct Krav Maga (Israeli self-defense), American Kickboxing, Tae Kwon Do and Muay Thai
- Level 2 Krav Maga certification and Instructor certifications through Premier Martial Arts International
- Teach seminars and run special events

### Responsibilities as Technical Support:

- Create training documents
- Compose templates for automated e-mails
- Troubleshoot computer issues and service printers at a basic level
- Coordinate all music played and maintained accounts - Spotify, Pandora, iTunes.

 Run social media, add new content, manage inquiries and keep up to date

#### Responsibilities as Manager:

- In charge of all part time instructors, front desk staff, and new hire training
- Coordinate instructor schedules
- Assign tasks/projects to other staff members and follow up on their work

#### Responsibilities in Marketing:

- Market for the sale of martial arts lessons, special events and promotional booths
- Promote events with business partnerships
- Built rapport with approximately 30 businesses

# Twin Eagle Consulting NOC Technician (Network Operations Center)

Centennial, Colorado January 2009 – October 2011

Twin Eagle Consulting is a group of consulting engineers with a focus on radio installation and monitoring. As a NOC Technician I was in charge of creating installation, radio layout and technical walk-through documentation. Monitoring radio networks for Police, Firefighters, Water and Oil Companies. Responsibilities included setting up notifications in the event that all or part of a client's radio network system went down, then contacting the appropriate crew to fix the issue. I oversaw construction of radio towers in oil fields and upon completion, setup and installed radio monitoring equipment. I also assisted in helping construct and implement Twin Eagle's Network Operations Center.

#### **EDUCATION**

Denver University - Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

#### **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

Martial Arts (Krav Maga), Parkour/Free Running, Camping and Backpacking, Snowboarding, Gaming, Science, Physics, Cooking, Playing Guitar, Piano, Drums, Cello, Bass, Movies, Solving Puzzles, Time with Friends

References available upon request